An incredible journey moving at the speed of sound.
August Rush is a family, drama, music film directed by Kirsten Sheridan.
Lyla and Louis, a singer and a musician, fall in love,
but are soon compelled to separate.
Lyla is forced to give up her newborn but unknown to her,
he grows up to become a musical genius.
August Rush, played by Freddie Highmore.
Lyla Novacek, played by Keri Russell.
Louis Connelly, played by Jonathan Rhys Meyers.
Richard Jeffries, played by Terrence Howard.
Maxwell "Wizard" Wallace, played by Robin Williams.
Thomas Novacek, played by William Sadler.
August Rush is a 2007 musical drama film directed by Kirsten
Sheridan and produced by Richard Barton Lewis.
The screenplay is by Nick Castle and James V.
Hart, with a story by Paul Castro and Castle.
It tells the story of an 11-year-old musical prodigy living in
an orphanage who runs away to New York City.
He begins to unravel the mystery of who he is, while his mother is
searching for him and his father is searching for her.
The many sounds and rhythms he hears throughout his journey culminate in a major
instrumental composition that concludes with his score, "August's Rhapsody".
The film explores themes of new york city, love of one's
life, guitar, composer, loss of loved one.
The tone is emotional.